<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>“The people who are crazy enough to think they can change the world are the ones who do" on My Digital Garden</title><link>https://casual-coderr.github.io/hugo-blog/</link><description>Recent content in “The people who are crazy enough to think they can change the world are the ones who do" on My Digital Garden</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 21 Aug 2022 17:17:08 +0530</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://casual-coderr.github.io/hugo-blog/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>(Day 1) Getting to know the exam</title><link>https://casual-coderr.github.io/hugo-blog/gre/day-1/</link><pubDate>Sun, 21 Aug 2022 17:17:08 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://casual-coderr.github.io/hugo-blog/gre/day-1/</guid><description>Hello World !! This is a custom in Programming to make the first thing as Hello World..
So Today is an important day, since i am starting two things parallelly, i am going to write this blog daily and update my work that i am doing and hopefully give the readers some motivation and even get some help if i am stuck at something.
Things i Did !</description></item><item><title>Paid Internships Through Nats-Portal</title><link>https://casual-coderr.github.io/hugo-blog/blog/nats-portal/</link><pubDate>Sun, 21 Aug 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://casual-coderr.github.io/hugo-blog/blog/nats-portal/</guid><description>Get yourself the skills the Industry Needs from Apprentice Training. First of all, what is NATS? NATS stands for National Apprenticeship Training Scheme. It is implemented by the MHRD. The government of India has mandated all the industries both private and public should engage some fresh graduates from colleges as Apprentices and train them.
This is a boon for many as freshers from colleges don’t usually have the know-hows and the skills required for working in the field right after college.</description></item><item><title>About</title><link>https://casual-coderr.github.io/hugo-blog/pages/about/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://casual-coderr.github.io/hugo-blog/pages/about/</guid><description>Hi there 👋👋 Nice to see you have found my blog.
My name is Rishikesh. I love creating stuff both Physical and Digital.
You can click on the Hamburger menu to read something new.</description></item></channel></rss>