<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Blog on My Digital Garden</title><link>https://casual-coderr.github.io/hugo-blog/blog/</link><description>Recent content in Blog on My Digital Garden</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 21 Aug 2022 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://casual-coderr.github.io/hugo-blog/blog/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Create your own Bit.ly Service Using Cloudflare Workers</title><link>https://casual-coderr.github.io/hugo-blog/blog/cloudflare-redirector/</link><pubDate>Mon, 22 Aug 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://casual-coderr.github.io/hugo-blog/blog/cloudflare-redirector/</guid><description>Do you use Bitly or Bit.ly Service ?
Mostly in your life you would have used any one of the link shortening services such as bitly, cuttly or any other service either for sharing a google doc or some article with a long link into a short one.
But the problem with bit.ly and other services is that you can’t customise the url portion like cutt.ly/rishi-is-awesome.
Even if you can customise it, you can’t change the origin url without using their premium plans.</description></item><item><title>(Day 1) Getting to know the exam</title><link>https://casual-coderr.github.io/hugo-blog/blog/day-1/</link><pubDate>Sun, 21 Aug 2022 17:17:08 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://casual-coderr.github.io/hugo-blog/blog/day-1/</guid><description>Hello World !! This is a custom in Programming to make the first thing as Hello World..
So Today is an important day, since i am starting two things parallelly, i am going to write this blog daily and update my work that i am doing and hopefully give the readers some motivation and even get some help if i am stuck at something.
Things I Learnt !! Why? Colleges require this to test canditates for their ability in reasoning and aptitude So To join MS need this ASAP.</description></item><item><title>Paid Internships Through Nats-Portal</title><link>https://casual-coderr.github.io/hugo-blog/blog/nats-portal/</link><pubDate>Sun, 21 Aug 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://casual-coderr.github.io/hugo-blog/blog/nats-portal/</guid><description>Get yourself the skills the Industry Needs from Apprentice Training. First of all, what is NATS? NATS stands for National Apprenticeship Training Scheme. It is implemented by the MHRD. The government of India has mandated all the industries both private and public should engage some fresh graduates from colleges as Apprentices and train them.
This is a boon for many as freshers from colleges don’t usually have the know-hows and the skills required for working in the field right after college.</description></item></channel></rss>